Overview

I'm a software engineer currently located in Brisbane, Australia. I have worked with a variety of technologies and frameworks that vary from simple mobile applications, to complex, cloud based, enterprise systems that integrate with multiple information systems.

I am originally from Venezuela and have been living in Australia for the last few years. I have with a growing interest in software design, building customer driven solutions, greenfield projects using cutting edge and disruptive technologies.

Technology and interests

- VueJS, Vuex, Nuxt, Angular, Webpack, Node.
- .NET, .NET Core, C#
- Microsoft Azure
- RESTful APIS
- Native and Hybrid Mobile Development
- HTML, CSS, LESS
- Javascript, ES6, Typescript

- iOS, Swift
- Inversion of Control
- OOP
- S.O.L.I.D Principles
- Design Patterns
- Source Control
- Agile Software Development
- GSAP and SVG

Professional Experience

Icon Group

Software Engineer 2016 – 2018

Worked with a complex cloud enterprise architecture, involving cloud services, message queues and RESTful APIs on Microsoft Azure.

Responsible for the design, implementation and delivery of full features including web application development, web API endpoints and on-premise services and database management.

Worked as an active member of two teams (Backend and Frontend). Overlooking code quality, mentoring and Leading the refactoring of a large legacy codebase moving to newer data driven frameworks VueJs.

Designed, Developed and maintained a full stack BackOffice solution using Angular, Material Design and .Net Core

Creative Curiosity

Software Developer Casual 2017

Worked as a Casual Software developer supporting the core development team in a variety of projects. Assisted with data migrations using Entity Framework, development of new features in existing projects build with ASP.NET and contributed to the development and delivery of projects using the Angular (4+) Framework including unit testing. Performed code reviews to maintain quality of code.

Designed, Developed and maintained a full stack BackOffice solution using Angular, Material Design and .Net Core

RightCrowd Software

Software Engineer 2015 - 2016

Involved in the development, implementation, maintenance and design of enterprise software. Worked as a full stack software engineer for leading software company in the physical security and compliance industry.

Involved in various projects for multinational companies, focusing on the Microsoft .NET framework and the design and development of solutions driven by web technologies.

App Factory

iOS Developer 2014 – 2015

Worked as part of a team to deliver iOS components for a hybrid mobile application using the ionic framework.

Responsible for the design, development, integration, delivery and maintenance of a native iOS localization plugin for a survey based mobile application.

Education

^{2012 - 2015} Masters of Information Technology Professional

Griffith University. Gold Coast, QLD Australia

2005 - 2012 Bachelor of Telecommunications Engineering

Universidad Andres Bello, Caracas, Venezuela

Achievements and Development

2014 Winner of the Opmantek Award for best Industry Project Semester 1 2014

2012 Publication:

"An interpolation method to calibrate electromagnetic probes in semi-anechoic

chambers,"

Progress In Electromagnetics Research B, Vol. 39, 355-371, 2012. ISSN: 1937-

6472.

2011 Speaker at IEEE student's congress, Maracaibo – Venezuela

Language Skills

Native Spanish, English (TOEFL score: 112/120)